Finding Aid for the S.A. Griffin collection of underground poetry, Scott Wannberg, and The Carma Bums LSC.2248
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writings collected by Griffin (Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box
  - Serials (Box 343, Box 344, Box 345, Box 116, Box 117, Box 118, Box 119, Box 120, Box 121, Box 122, Box 123, Box 124, Box 125, Box 126, Box 127, Box 128, Box 129, Box 130, Box 131, Box 132, Box 133, Box 134, Box 135, Box 136, Box 137, Box 138, Box 139, Box 140, Box 141, Box 142, Box 143, Box 144,
    - Subculture Magazine, no. 4. Whittier., 1994 September/October (Box 146, Folder 5)
      This bimonthly journal dedicated to Latino culture, music and lifestyle is published and edited by Steve Martinez and includes features on El Grito, Joe Servantez, JV the "Nayba'Hood Queen," and Proposition 187, the "Save Our State" initiative.
    - Suitcase, v. 1, no. 1-2. Los Angeles., 1995 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      This "journal of transcultural traffic" is signed to Griffin by founder/editor/designer Babak Nahid.
    - Sulfur, v. 2, no. 1, issue 4. Pasadena., 1982 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Sulfur, v. 10, no. 2, issue 27. Pasadena., 1990 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Sunset Palms Hotel, v. 1, no. 2. Santa Monica., 1973 Summer (Box 146, Folder 8)
      Michael C. Ford's Mt. Alverno Press published nine issues of Sunset Palms Hotel between 1973 and 1983.
      Michael C. Ford edited this issue with Bill Yaryan and Colman Andrews. This issue features "more used cars and more racket gals exposed." The title page features the following words from James Jameson: "The Sunset Palms hotel/ Or the Hollywood Psalms hotel/ Or the smell of hell motel/ Go tell your name/ Los Angeles."
    - Sunset Palms Hotel, v. 1, no. 3. Santa Monica., 1973 Winter (Box 146, Folder 8)
      This charted and uncharted territories issue includes travelogues by the following: Ahmos Zu Bolton III, Eloise Klein Healy, Manuel Bandeira, Douglas Blazek, and Ronald Koertge.
    - Sunset Palms Hotel, v. 2, no. 4. Santa Monica., 1974 Spring (Box 146, Folder 8)
      This Electric Academic issue includes poems from the following guests: Luis Campos, Wanda Coleman, Eloise Klein Healy, Tom Waits, Alison Sky, and Ronald Koertge. This issue features pen and ink drawings on the cover and within by Charles Bukowski.-
    - Sunset Palms Hotel, v. 2, no. 5. Santa Monica., 1974 Summer (Box 146, Folder 8)
      This Murder in the Academy issue is dedicated to Stuart Z. Perkoff and includes work by Harry E Northup, Liza Williams, Michael McClure, Miriam Simos, and William Pillin.
    - Sunset Palms Hotel, v. 3, no. 6. Santa Monica., 1975 Summer (Box 146, Folder 8)
      This Silent Movies issue is dedicated to the memory of Lawrence Lipton and includes work by Bob Greenfield, F.A. Nettlebeck, Bill Morrison, Gerald Locklin, Charles R. Hockett, Brad Darby, and Lyn Lifshin.
    - Sushi By The Pool, no. 2. Canoga Park., undated (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Swill. Claremont., undated (Box 146, Folder 10)
      Swill is a publication produced by students of Pomona College.
    - Synaesthesia, no. 4. Hickory., 1991 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - The Tale Of: "God To The Rescue Of The Earth!" no. 1. Los Angeles., 1991 January 20 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Tales From The Zone. Los Angeles., 1991 - 1999 (Box 146, Folder 13)
      This is the official newsletter of the L.A. Cacophony Society. According to the front page, the Society's members state the following: "We are the new merry pranksters providing an escape hatch for people caught up in the grid of modern life. The Cacophony Society has no rules and no leaders. You may already be a member!"
      1991 (January and July/August), no. 4 (undated), no. 6 (1991 December), no. 10 (1992 April), no. 14 (1992 August), no. 16 (1992 October), no. 20 (1993 February), no. 29 (1993 November), no. 30 (1993 December), no. 32 (1994 February), no. 43 (1995 January), no. 47-48 (1995 May-June), no. 56 (1996 February), no. 63 (1996 October), no. 64 (1996 November), no. 71 (1996 June), no. 86 (1998 September), no. 87 (1998 October), no. 98 (1999 September).
    - A Taste Of Justice, v. 1, no. 1. Hollywood., 1990 Summer (Box 147, Folder 1)
      Poems by Justice Howard.
    - A Taste Of Justice, v. 1, no. 2. Hollywood., 1990 Fall (Box 147, Folder 1)
      "Memoirs While Reaching Up To Play Handball On The Curb" by Justice Howard.
    - Tears In The Fence, no. 44-46, 48-49. Blandford Forum, circa 2007-2009 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Temper, v. 1., 1992 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Testicle Pressure, v. 8, no. 1. Rego Park., 1994 August (Box 147, Folder 5)
      One audiocassette.
      This zine is accompanied by a Propulsion Records Exploitation audiocassette.
    - Theatre Historical Society of America, no. 14. Elmhurst., 1987 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Theatre Historical Society of America, no. 30. Elmhurst., 2003 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - the-hold.com, no. 35. Deptford., 2000 August (Box 147, Folder 7)
      This issue is dedicated to Michael McNeilley.
    - Third Lung Review, no. 3, 4, 6, 10, 12, 13, 15, 17-19. Conover, 1988-90, 1994-97 (Box 147, Folder 8)
      Third Lung Review began as an annual publication that coincided with the Third Lung Press Poetry Contest.
    - This Is Important, no. 10. Los Angeles., 1985 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      Illuminati is Peter Schneidre's small press handle. According to Griffin, Schneidre published hundreds and hundreds of quality titles in his time.
      This issue is edited by F.A. Nettelbeck and published by Illuminati. It contains work by John Levin, Susan Osterman, Jack Micheline, Ron Androla, Mitchell Rhodes, and Todd Moore.
    - Thought, no. 1., 2000 April (Box 148, Folder 2)
      This publication features an excerpt from a history paper written by a cat on LSD.
    - Thought For Food, editions 3 and 4. Los Angeles., circa 1989 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      This zine was created by Exene Cervenka.
    - Time, v. 73, no. 6. Chicago., 1959 February 9 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Time. New York., 2001 September 11 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Tits & Clits, no. 7. Berkeley., 1987 November (Box 148, Folder 5)
      This comic was created by Joyce Farmer and Mary Fleener.
    - TO, v. 1, no. 1. Narberth., 1992 (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - TO, v. 1, no. 2. Narberth., 1993 (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - Tobey C. Moss Gallery. Los Angeles., 2005 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      This catalog is the From George Herms With Love exhibition of Assemblage, Collage, and Prints from the last of the Los Angeles "Beat" Culture. This catalog is signed by George Herms.
    - Toltec Poetry Review. North Hollywood., 1990 July/August - November/December (Box 148, Folder 7)
      This program/journal focuses on "Free, Positive, Constructive, and Supportive" poetry workshops at the Lankershim Arts Center.
    - Too Much Coffee Man Full Color Special, no. 1. Austin., 1996 July (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Tortilla, v. 2. Maywood., 1994 Winter (Box 148, Folder 9)
      Tortilla is a non-profit publication created and funded by Aida Salazar. It is published and distributed quarterly,
      This is a Chicano/Lation based publication with contributors such as Eddie Torres, La Malinche, Sly, Ricardo Nathaniel Santos, Heather Gonzalez, Alma Rosa Alvarez, and Ruth Razo.
    - Traffic Report. Santa Monica., 1998 April (Box 148, Folder 10)
      This 18th Street Art Complex publication includes a feature on Self Help Graphics and work by Luis Alfaro, Pleasant Gehman, Gustavo Alberto Garcia Vaca, Barbara J. Genovese, Ellyn Maybe, and Eric C. Wat.
    - Transit, no. 1. North Coventry., 1993 Spring (Box 148, Folder 11)
      This Beat Scene publication includes writing by Charles Bukowski, Jack Micheline, Charles Plymell, and John Montgomery.
    - Transit, no. 2. North Coventry., 1993 Summer (Box 148, Folder 11)
      This Beat Scene publication includes writing by Charles Bukowski, Jack Micheline, Jack Kerouac, and Anne Waldman.
    - Transit, no. 3. North Coventry., 1993 Late Summer (Box 148, Folder 11)
      This Beat Scene publication is a Jack Kerouac Special issue.
    - Transit, no. 4. North Coventry., 1993 Autumn (Box 148, Folder 11)
      This Beat Scene publication is the Carolyn Cassady interview issue.
    - Transit, no. 5. North Coventry., 1994 early (Box 148, Folder 11)
      This Beat Scene publication includes writing from Charles Bukowski, Jack Kerouac, and Philip Whalen.
    - Transit, no. 7. North Coventry., 1996 November (Box 148, Folder 11)
      This Beat Scene publication features writing by Diane di Prima, A.D. Winans, Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Anne Waldman, and Edie Kerouac Parker.
    - Transit, no. 9. North Coventry., 1999 Winter (Box 148, Folder 12)
      This Beat Scene publication features writing by Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Diane di Prima, Gerald Nicosia, Janine Pommy Vega, and Linda King.
    - Transit, no. 10. North Coventry., 2002 Spring (Box 148, Folder 12)
      This Beat Scene publication features writing by Charles Bukowski, Michael McClure, Anne Waldman, Aram Saroyan, Charles Plymell, A.D. Winans, Jack Kerouac, Neal Cassady, and Billy Childish.
    - Transit, no. 11. North Coventry., 2002 Summer (Box 148, Folder 12)
      This Beat Scene publication features writing by Michael McClure, Joanne Kyger, Janine Pommy Vega, Charles Plymell, and Lawrence Ferlinghetti.
    - Trngkt, no. 1., 2009 May (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Tsunami, v. 2, no. 2. Venice., 1989 Spring (Box 148, Folder 14)
      Tsunami is published by Earthquake Press and includes writing from Amy Uyematsu, Cherry Jean Vasconcellos, Marcia Cohee, and Denise Dumars.
    - Tsunami, v. 3, no. 1. Venice., 1990 Winter (Box 148, Folder 14)
      This issue features "The Next Wave" in which the editors discuss the last fifteen years of poetry in Los Angeles.
    - Tsunami, v. 3, no. 2. Venice., 1990 Summer (Box 148, Folder 14)
      This issue features work from Paula Thompson, Regina Rocca, Laurel Ann Bogen, Michael C. Ford, Lisa D. Chavez, and Ellyn Maybe.
    - Turning The Tide, v. 27, no. 1. Culver City., 2014 January-March (Box 148, Folder 15)
      This journal is published by the Inter-Communal Solidarity Committee.
    - TV Click. Portland., 1989 October 15-21 (Box 193, Folder 15)
    - Twin Palms Publishers. Santa Fe., 1993 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Under Pant, v. 2., 1999 (Box 148, Folder 16)
      Poems and illustrations by Paddy Campanaro.
    - The Understated, no. 3. Los Angeles., 2002 March (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - The ULC News, v. 36, no. 5. Modesto., 1998 Fall (Box 148, Folder 18)
      This Universal Life Church (ULC) newsletter is published quarterly from the ULC's international headquarters in Modesto, California.
    - The Unquiet Desperation, v. 1, no. 13., 2007 May (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Unt-Cay, no. 0., 1994 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - UnTV, no. 1. Glendale., 1992 Fall (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Up On The Roof, v. 1, no. 4. Denver., undated (Box 149, Folder 4)
      Up On The Roof is the magazine of the Urban Peak Creative Writing Workshop.
    - Urban Explorer, v. 2, no. 1. Culver City., 1994 January (Box 149, Folder 5)
      This issue includes a feature on Abbot Kinney's Venice.
    - URTHKIN, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1978 March (Box 149, Folder 6)
      This issue is edited and published by Larry Ziman and typed by Gertrude Dwyer.
    - Vacancy, no. 3. Valparaiso., 2006 Summer (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Vagabond, v. 1, no. 2. Rosemead., 1999 Spring (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Vagabond White Paper, no. 5. Santa Monica., circa 1983 (Box 149, Folder 9)
      This issue features Bern Porter interviewed by Phil Nurenberg. It is signed by Nurenberg, "a fan of The Tribe," to Mister and Missus Mike Bruner.
    - Veins, v. 1, no. 1. Philadelphia., 1994 Spring (Box 149, Folder 10)
      This issue features "Remnants of Labor Day" and "Anything Baby" by L.A.'s Punk Hostage Press pioneer Iris Berry.
    - Venice Thirteen, v. 1, no. 1. Venice., 1994 Spring (Box 149, Folder 11)
      This is a communal project printed by Bayrock Press which contains the work of thirteen members of the Venice Poetry Workshop.
      This issue is signed by Luis Campos.
    - Verve, v. 2, nos. 1-3; v. 3 nos. 1-4. Simi Valley, 1990 Spring - 1991 Winter (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Vice Versa, v. 4, nos. 1-3; v. 5, nos. 1-3. Chicago, 1989-1990 (Box 149, Folder 14)
      This "zine of the times" published poetry and short stories.
    - Village View, v. 6, no. 31. Los Angeles., 1992 March 6-12 (Box 149, Folder 15)
      This issue features a cover story on Harry Crews.
    - Violent Virgins, no. 16. Pittsburgh., undated (Box 149, Folder 16)
      This issue features poems in dialogue by Rane Arroyo and Paul Weinman.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 1. Newhall., 1983 Spring (Box 150, Folder 1)
      This is a new quarterly published by Los Angeles Poets' Press (LAPP). According to the editorial poem, this publication is "a magazine of poetic persuasions & uncharted visual adventures." The Coordinating Editor for this issue is Luis Campos.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 2. Newhall., 1983 Summer (Box 150, Folder 1)
      This issue features Coordinating Editor Richard J. Weekly.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. A. Newhall., 1984 June (Box 150, Folder 1)
      This issue is edited by Richard J. Weekly and features poems by John "Jack" Brander. It is signed to Griffin by Brander.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 4. Newhall., 1984 June (Box 150, Folder 1)
      This issue's Coordinating Editor is Tina Megali.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 5. Newhall., 1984 Fall (Box 150, Folder 1)
      This issue's Coordinating Editor is Richard J. Weekley.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 8. Newhall., 1986 Spring (Box 150, Folder 2)
      Coordinating Editors for this issue are Richard J. Weekley and Tina Landrum Megali.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 9. Newhall., undated (Box 150, Folder 2)
      Coordinating Editor for this issue is Jerry Danielsen.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 10. Newhall., 1987 (Box 150, Folder 2)
      This issue is edited by Richard J. Weekley, Rina Landrum Megali, and Jerry Danielsen with assistance from Spiritual Advisor Heidi York.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 11. Newhall., 1987 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 12. Newhall., 1988 Spring (Box 150, Folder 2)
      Coordinating Editors for this issue are Richard J. Weekley and Tina Megali. The cover features a graphic for "Wind and Water and Stone" by Octavio Paz.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 13. Newhall., 1989 Winter (Box 150, Folder 3)
      The Coordinating Editor for this issue is Tina Megali.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 14. Newhall., 1989 (Box 150, Folder 3)
      The Coordinating Editor for this issue is Heidi York.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 15. Newhall., 1990 Winter (Box 150, Folder 3)
      The Coordinating Editor for this issue is Jerry Danielsen.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 16. Newhall., 1990 Spring (Box 150, Folder 3)
      Richard J. Weekley is the Coordinating Editor for this issue dedicated to William Stafford.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 17. Newhall., 1990 Fall (Box 150, Folder 4)
      The Coordinating Editor for this issue is Donald McLeod.
    - VOL. NO. Magazine, no. 18. Newhall., 1991 Fall (Box 150, Folder 4)
      The Coordinating Editor for this "Between a Poet & a Hard Spot" issue is Donald McLeod.
    - Warner Grand Theatre. San Pedro., 2001 January (Box 150, Folder 5)
      This program was published for the 70th Anniversary Celebration of the theatre.
    - Water Row Books Catalogue, no. 72. Sudbury., 1997 (Box 150, Folder 6)
      Water Row Books is a bookseller and publisher specializing in Beat books, graphix, used/new/rare, and avant-garde literature since 1982.
    - Water Row Books Catalogue, no. 73. Sudbury., 1998 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Weak, no. 3. Santa Cruz., undated (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - West Coast Poetry Review, issue 12, v. 3, no. 4. Reno., 1974 (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - Westways, v. 100, no. 1. Santa Ana., 2008 January/February (Box 150, Folder 8)
      This issue's cover feature is on L.A.'s historic movie palaces.
    - Whoreson Dog, no. 1. Pasadena., 1993 Spring (Box 150, Folder 9)
      This issue edited by Mark Thorpe and Dennis Nishi includes the following writers: Lyn Lifshin, Marael Johnson, Gerald Locklin, Bill Mohr, Todd Moore, Belinda Subraman, Bayla Winters, Michael C. Ford, and Charles Bukowski.
    - Wicked Mission, no. 3. Moreno Valley., undated (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Wicked Mission, no. 3.5. Moreno Valley., undated (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Wildflowers, v. 10. Woodstock., 2009 Summer Solstice (Box 150, Folder 11)
      This Woodstock mountain poetry anthology includes work by Lee Ann Brown, Andy Clausen, Hettie Jones, Louise Landes Levi, Thurston Moore, Marc Olmsted, and Janine Pommy Vega. This issue is signed by Olmsted.
    - William Blake: Book Illustrator, v. 1. Normal., 1972 (Box 344, Folder 9)
    - WIRE, v. 10. Highland Park., 1990 Fall/1991 Winter (Box 150, Folder 12)
      This issue In Memoriam: Lorri Jackson (1962-1990) and Thomas McGrath (1916-1990).
    - The Word. Richardson., 1997 January (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Words Dance, no. 13., 2013 Summer (Box 151, Folder 2)
      This poetry mag edited by Amanda Oaks and includes writing by A. Razor, Carrie Rudzinski, John Dorsey, and Shinji Moon.
    - Work, no. 1. Granada Hills., circa 2004 (Box 151, Folder 3)
      This zine is signed to Griffin by Xerox cover artist Rob Zabrecky.
    - The Wormwood Review, v. 29, no. 1, issue 113. Stockton., 1989 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - The Wormwood Review, v. 30, no. 1, issue 117. Stockton., 1990 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - The Wormwood Review, v. 36, no. 3, issue 143. Stockton., 1996 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      This issue features Gerald Locklin's The Last Round-Up.
    - Xylophone, no. 2., circa 1989 (Box 151, Folder 6)
      Correspondence from Tony to Griffin is inserted into this issue.
    - Young and Stoned, no. 2. Los Angeles., undated (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Zap Comix, no. 8. San Francisco., 1975 (Box 151, Folder 8)
      This issue features cover art by R. Crumb.
    - Zap Comix, no. 10. San Francisco., 1982 (Box 151, Folder 8)
      This issue features illustrations by R. Crumb.
    - Zap Comix, no. 11. San Francisco., 1985 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Zeal Magazine, v. 1, no. 2. Long Beach., 1999 Spring (Box 151, Folder 9)
      This issue includes features on Wicca, the one day heroin detox phenomenon, and Russians in L.A.
    - Zeal Magazine, v. 1, no. 4. Long Beach., 1999 Fall (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Zen Baby, no. 19. Santa Cruz., circa 2008 (Box 151, Folder 10)
      This zine by Christopher Robin features a photo of Griffin on the inside of the back cover with the following caption: "S.A. Griffin Gets Kinky ZB Zine & Stumpfucker Calvacade."
    - Zendik Farm. Boulevard., circa 1988-1990 (Box 151, Folder 11)
      This is the official publication of the Zendik Farm Arts Commune. This folder contains three issues.
    - Zip Code, no. 1-3. Northampton, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Zomoid, v. 1, no. 7. Los Angeles., 1984 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Zomoid, v. 3, no. 3. Los Angeles., 1984 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Zygote In My Coffee, no. 2. Kettering., 2006 Fall (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Zygote In My Coffee, no. 100. Kettering., 2008 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - ZYZZYVA, v. 15, no. 1. San Francisco., 1999 Spring (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - Manuscripts, circa 1965-2012 (Box 154, Box 155, Box 156, Box 157, Box 158, Box 159)
    These manuscripts, which are organized alphabetically by author, include poetry submissions by writers such as Wanda Coleman, Laurel Ann Bogen, francEyE, and Todd Moore sent to Griffin for consideration for The Outlaw Bible of American Poetry and periodicals Griffin published, as well as drafts and galleys of materials published by Rose of Sharon Press. Some folders include correspondence to Griffin and ephemera shared with him.
    - Alamares, Jay, 1998 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Albertano, Linda, 1993 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Alfonso, Chris, undated (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Alvarado, Rafael FJ, 1989-1993 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Amram, David, 1999 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Ayres, Justin (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Bauer, Jeff (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Bearis, Ency, 2010 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Bell, Miles T., 2006 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Bender, Skie, 1988 August (Box 154, Folder 10)
      This folder also includes manuscripts by Kathi Georges and Tony Vaughan.
    - Bennett, John, 2000 January (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Bogen, Laurel Ann, 2000, undated (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Branaman, Bob, 1998-1999 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Brewer, Jack, 1991, undated (Box 154, Folder 14-15)
      Griffin met Jack Brewer at an X=Art show that they were both booked on and have remained friends. For many years Brewer would improvise on guitar while Griffin worked the words. Brewer created The Lofty Canaanites sometime in the early 2000s, an improvisational punk/jazz band with Joe Baiza, Steve Reed, and Bob Lee with Brewer and Griffin as the front men. Bob Lee was replaced by Brian Christopherson for future incarnations.
    - Brown, Eric, 1992, undated (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Brown, Kenneth H., 1965 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - Bruner, Michael Lane, undated, 1992, 1996, 2005 (Box 154, Folder 18-20)
      Michael Lane Bruner is a friend of Griffin's who he met at The Water Espresso Gallery during the early 1980s in Hollywood. Bruner, Griffin, Doug Knott, and Mike M. Mollett created The Lost Tribe. Later, with Bobbo Staron and Scott Wannberg, they reformed as The Carma Bums. Still working together, most recently as The Lost Bums (Bruner, Griffin, Knott, and Mollett) they created a CD of readings and spontaneous raps produced by Bruner The Lost Bums: Ozark Revelations (2016) and forthcoming The Hideous Bible (Rose of Sharon). Griffin published and edited Bruner's book Natural Geographics (Rose of Sharon) in 2014. Bruner is now the head of admissions at Georgia State University. While working towards his double Masters at the University of Washington, Seattle in 1994, Bruner would bring The Carma Bums into the new frontier of the Internet via the tech department at the university resulting in The Carma Bums International Superhighway Tour of Words, considered the first poetry website of its kind featuring original writing, graphic images, and hyperlinks.
    - Caldera, Leslie, 1993 (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - Campbell, Pris, undated (Box 154, Folder 22)
    - Castro, Fernando D., 1993 (Box 154, Folder 23)
    - Cherkovski, Neeli, 1988 (Box 154, Folder 24)
      This folder contains a copy of "Charles Bukowski Notes On A Dirty Old Man" with Cherkovski's annotations and edits. This document is signed by Cherkovski.
    - Coca, Peter, undated (Box 154, Folder 25-26)
    - Cohee, Marcia, 1993, undated (Box 154, Folder 27-28)
    - Cohol, Alan, 1988 (Box 155, Folder 1)
      This folder also contains a manuscript by Jerry Gordon.
    - Coleman, Wanda, undated (Box 155, Folder 2)
      In addition to "South Central Death Trip," this folder contains four "unpublished" poems.
    - Collins, Billy, 1998 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Collins, Cait, 1998 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Cruz, Dennis, undated (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - DeJure, Marcel, 1998-2000 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Dernbach, T., circa 1999 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - DeWitt, Jim, undated (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Donnelly, Jim, 1988 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Doten, Don, 2010 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Ferguson, Rich, undated (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Field, Edward, 1998 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Fleck, John, undated (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Foley, Jack, 2000 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Ford, Michael C., circa 1989 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Formosa, Kathryn, 1999 (Box 155, Folder 16)